hdtvtest.co.uk 2017-06-06

# HDTVTest: Privacy Policy

This is a privacy policy for _hdtvtest.co.uk_ , a wholly owned website of **HDTVTest Limited (Company No. 07251203** ). Our homepage is located at [http://www.hdtvtest.co.uk](http://www.hdtvtest.co.uk/).

Our postal address is HDTVTest Ltd, 12 St Pauls Road, Manchester M20 4PG; we can be reached via e-mail at info AT hdtvtest.co.uk.

## Privacy Policy Table Of Content

  * Identifiable & Non-Identifiable Information
  * Cookies
  * Security
  * Policy Change
  * How You Can Access & Correct Your Information
  * How To Contact Us

### Identifiable & Non-Identifiable Information 

At the time of visiting our website or submiting email to _hdtvtest.co.uk_ , we may collect identifiable personal information such as your IP address, name and email address as well as non-identifiable information including, but not limited to, operating system, browser type, domain name, site access times and referring web site address.

Identifiable information is used:

  * To allow customers access to restricted areas of our site.
  * To protect our services and rights.
  * To enable us to answer queries or provide a specific service.

_hdtvtest.co.uk_ uses non identifiable information for the purposes of business analysis, marketing and promotional purposes.

We will not make your identifiable personal information available to third parties unless required to do so by law.

### Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored locally on your computer and contains information about your activities on the Internet. On our website, we use cookies to track users' progress through the site, allowing us to make improvements based on usage data. The information in a cookie does not contain any personally identifiable information you submit to our site.

Once you close your browser, our access to the cookie terminates. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose not to accept the cookie, this will not affect your access to the majority of information available on our website. However, you may not be able to make full use of our online services.

### Security

When we transfer and receive certain types of sensitive information such as financial or health information, we redirect visitors to a secure server and will notify visitors through a pop-up screen on our site. We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.

### Policy Change

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our website to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our website periodically.

Customers may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by e-mailing us at the above address.

### How You Can Access And Correct Your Information 

Upon request we provide site visitors with access to contact information (e.g., name, address, phone number) that we maintain about them .

Consumers can access this information by e-mail us at the above address. Upon request we offer visitors the ability to have inaccuracies corrected in contact information.

Consumers can have this information corrected by sending us e-mail at the above address. 

### How To Contact Us 

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above postal address or email.
